toppng.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy Policy - TOPpng

* * *

The owners and operators of TOPpng.com take your online privacy seriously. This document outlines the types of information collected by our servers and provides links to the privacy policies of our third-party advertising partners.

### User Accounts

Membership is an optional part of the TOPpng.com web site. No user account is required in order to browse or download the content we provide. However, creating an account enables extra features such as (but not limited to) the ability to submit content.

By creating an account, you are volunteering certain information about yourself that will be stored on our servers. This data includes at a minimum a username, password, and valid email address. Your user profile information is public and may appear on our web site, with the exception of your email address and password.

Our commenting feature allows non-registered users to post comments. In these cases we display the provided name associated with the comment. It is up to you to ensure that your username/email address is anonymous.

### Personally Identified Data

We strongly discourage users from entering their full name, phone number, physical address, or other sensitive information in user profiles, comments, or other areas of the site. Furthermore, we request that minors and any individuals with limited decision making ability not create an account on this site without the approval and supervision of a guardian.

We make a reasonable attempt to monitor for cases where users post personally identifiable information about other individuals to public portions of the web site and remove the offending material.

### Server Logs

Like most web sites, TOPpng.com logs web, database, and other server-software usage and access information. This information may include your internet protocol (IP) address, which in many cases can be translated to an affiliation (such as your work, school, or internet service provider), or a geographical location. We only use this information for debugging purposes and for aggregating into anonymous usage and traffic statistics.

### Cookies

You should be aware that when you use our websites, mobile sites, or mobile apps, we may collect information by using 'cookies'. By using our websites, mobile sites, or mobile apps, you accept the use of cookies as described below.

What are Cookies?

Cookies are small text files placed on your computer when you browse a website. Your browser sends these cookies back to the website every time you visit the site again, so it can recognize you and can then tailor what you see on the screen.

Why use cookies?

Cookies are an important part of the internet. They make using websites much smoother and affect lots of the useful features of websites. Some cookies are essential so you can move around the website and use its features. Without these cookies, services you have asked for cannot be provided. These cookies do not gather information about you that could be used for marketing or remembering where you have been on the internet.

A group of cookies, often called 'analytics cookies' are used to gather information about how people navigate (find their way through) our sites. These cookies do not collect information that identifies you. The information collected is anonymous and is grouped with the information from everyone else’s cookies. We can then see the overall patterns of usage rather than any one person’s activity. Analytics cookies only record activity on the site you are on and they are only used to improve how a website works.

We use cookies in order to remember your choices, to give you a better user experience by improving our web sites and for providing content more accurately suited to your needs. Cookies allow a more detailed level of tracking that helps us to gain a better understanding of potential areas for improvement so as to continually improve the relevance of and accessibility of the content we provide.

This means we use cookies in order to remember:

  * Your browser settings, such as the type of browser you use and what plug-ins you have installed. This keeps us from bothering you every time you enter the site in order to make sure that you have the necessary equipment to download information from our sites. It also allows us to know how many people are using certain types of software, so that we can adjust our site to provide the best browsing experience for every visitor.
  * Your language and region choice. This means that if you have once chosen English as a language this is the default language that will be used when you revisits us.
  * The last time we asked you to participate in a survey and whether you answered it so we do not prompt you too often.
  * Your movement on and usage of our sites. We do not collect personal data as part of this. We collect statistical data so we can optimize our site.
  * Recently used data - to improve performance. In case we store personal data in a cookie, the information will be encrypted and thus safe.

How to avoid and delete cookies?

If you do not want us to place or read cookies on your computer, you can deselect cookies in your browser where you can select the cookies that are to be allowed, blocked or deleted. If you are using a PC and a recent browser and you want to remove the cookies that are already placed on your computer, press CTRL + SHIFT + DELETE at the same time.

If the hot keys do not work in your browser, visit the support site of the relevant browser. If you choose not to accept cookies at all, you can still visit our website, however we cannot guarantee an optimum experience without cookies.

Google

[How Google uses data when you use its partners' sites or apps](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/)  
You also have the option to opt out of Google Analytics data collection. [Click here to know more.](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)

### Third-Party Advertisers

TOPpng.com serves ads provided by a range of third-party advertising networks. The practices of our advertising partners are not directly covered by TOPpng.com's privacy policy. We recommend that you read their policies. For your convenience we provide a list our advertising partners below. Unfortunately we cannot guarantee it is always comprehensive and up to date.

> Google AdSense 
> 
> Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

### Sharing/Selling of Data

TOPpng.com does NOT share or sell personally identifiable data to third parties such as direct marketers. We respect your privacy.

### Account Cancellation

Upon request, your TOPpng.com account can be canceled. Your user profile will no longer appear on the web site and your submissions will no longer be listed publicly for download. Any comments you have posted will still appear, but will not be linked to your profile. After cancellation, you will be not be available for log-in.

### Data Retention

The data submitted to and generated by this web site may be copied to additional machines for redundancy and backup purposes.
